Guide to the Dale R. Corson papers, 1963-1977
Corson, Dale R. papers, 1963-1977
- Series I. Administrative Papers
  - Administrative Papers 1963-1969
    - Office of the Controller, 1966-67 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      Peterson, Arthur H. Workmen's Compensation; Group life insurance.
    - Office of the Controller - Payroll Function, 1965-6 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Work Week., 1966-67 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Fayette County Project, 1965-66 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      Doar, John J.; Dowd, Douglas F. United States Department of Justice - Civil Rights Division; Fayette County Fund.
    - Haskins Laboratory, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Levin, Harry.
    - Higher Education Bill of 1965, 1965-66 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Risley, Robert F.; Palm, Charles E.; Robison, Howard W.; Kuusisto, Allan A.; McCurdy, Charles P. "Cornell University Series of Films on Higher Education"; Association of Research Libraries.
    - Cornell University Libraries, 1955-63 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      McCarthy, Stephen A. Library Board; Supplementary Book Funds.
    - Cornell University Libraries, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      McCarthy, Stephen A.; Miller, J. Gormly; Pacheco, Felipe R.; Keast, William R. Library Board.
    - Cornell University Libraries, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      McCarthy, Stephen A.; Reichmann, Felix. Association of Research Libraries; Olin Library operations; Federal support; Reclassification.
    - Cornell University Libraries, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      Fox, Edith M.; Littel, Edward G.; McCarthy, Stephen A.; Tierney, Brian; Healey, George H.; Rockefeller, Nelson A. Regional History storage in Old Mill; Reclassification; Ford Foundation.
    - Systems and Procedures, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Administrative Internship - Thomas E. Baker, 1967-68 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      Wilson, Logan. American Council on Education; Sindler Commission.
    - Administrative Internship Program - Ellis L. Phillips Foundation, 1964-65 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      Adams, Arthur; Vinocur, Jacob.
    - National Science Foundation, 1959-64 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      Rogers, Thomas R.; Boynton, Damon; Comar, Cyril L.; Atwood, Sanford S.
    - Nuclear Technology in Public Affairs.Eipper, Alfred W. Cornell Center for Study of the Influence of Nuclear Technology in Public Affairs (Proposed), 1960-68 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Remington Rand Univac, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      Shriver, A. R. Computers.
    - Hospital Administration Research Program, 1957-66 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      Allen, James E.; Summerskill, John. Sloan Institute.
    - Research Associates, 1960-68 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      Long, Franklin A.; Rogers, Thomas R.
    - Social Science Research Center, 1965-66 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      Thompson, Wayne E.; Macklin, David; Muller, Steven.
    - Special Projects Committee., 1966 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Special Projects Committee., 1966-67 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - New York State Technical Services Act of 1965. Davenport, Donald H., 1965 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - New York State College of Agriculture Academic Plan, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - New York State College of Home Economics Academic Plan., 1966 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations Academic Plan., 1966 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - New York State Veterinary College. Academic Plan., 1966 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - State University of New York, 1958-66 (Box 15, Folder 28)
      Syrett, Harold C.; Peterson, Arthur H. Council on Economic Growth, Technology, and Public Policy of the Committee on Institutional Cooperation.
    - SUNY. Porter, Harry W.; Syrett, Harold C.; Gould, Samuel B.; Perkins, James A. Cornell-SUNY relationship; SUNY Master Plan; Committee on Institutional Cooperation., 1966 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - SUNY. Gould, Samuel B.; Larsson, Robert; Porter, Harry W.; Peterson, Arthur H. New York State College of Agriculture., 1967 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - SUNY. Syrett, Harold C.; Kennedy, W. Keith; Gould, Samuel B.; Stamp, Neal R. Cornell University Medical College; Cornell University-SUNY relationship., 1967 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Dorothy Green vs. State of New York., 1958-67 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Student-Alumni Study, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 33)
      Marcham, John; Jackson, R. Peter.
    - Students for Education, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 34)
      Alexander, Robert C.; Pearlman, Robert S.; Kahn, Alfred E. Student activism; Student protest.
    - Students for Education, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 35)
      Weiss, Burton Ira; Bennett, James E.; Eissner, Bruce A.; Davis, Stanley W.; Alexander, Robert C.; Kahn, Alfred E.; Perkins, James A.
    - Executive Board of Student Government, 1966-67 (Box 15, Folder 36)
      Birchall, Richard.
    - Executive Board of Student Government., 1967-68 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - SCARB (Scheduling, Coordination and Activities Review Board), 1967-68 (Box 15, Folder 38)
      Barlow, Mark; Levy, Stanley R.; Shapiro, Arthur M.; Birchall, Richard. Fall Mobilization in Washington; Student Referendum; Student funds; SCARB Constitution.
    - Taxes, 1964-65 (Box 15, Folder 39)
      Williams, David B.; Morris, James; Parratt, Lyman G. Foreign visitors' tax and visa matters; Stipends for Graduate Student Assistants.
    - University Health Services, 1955-64 (Box 15, Folder 40)
      Bridge, Donald; Miller, Paul A.; Durland, Lewis H.; Moore, Norman S. Gannett Medical Clinic; Gannett Foundation; Sage Hospital; Accreditation; Gannett Clinic expansion.
    - University Health Services, 1965-67 (Box 15, Folder 41)
      Moore, Norman S.; Bridge, Donald; Long, Franklin A. Christian Science practitioners; Accreditation; Ad Hoc Committee on Speech and Drama; Student insurance; Gannett Foundation; By-laws of Sage Hospital and Gannett Clinic.
    - University Airplane., 1964-66 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - University Airplane, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 43)
      Burton, John E.; Wright, Theodore P.
    - Six-Year Ph. D. s - Housing, 1965-67 (Box 15, Folder 44)
      Parrish, Stephen M.; Tinsley, Adrian; Morris, Edward P. Residential Club fire.
    - Residential Club Fire, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 45)
      Will, Philip; Benardette, Diego; Muller, Steven; Dean, Arthur H.
    - Residential Club Fire - Thank You Letters., 1967 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Residential Club Fire - Dale Corson's Notes., 1967 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Residential Club Fire - Deceased. Stamp, Neal R. Sage Chapel memorial plaque; Liability claims; Smith litigation; Tuition refunds; Memorial Service; University statements., 1967-68 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Residential Club Fire - Inquest, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 49)
      Muller, Steven; Tobin, Thomas L. Code violations.
    - Residential Club Fire - Fire Reports, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 50)
      Burton, John E.
    - Residential Club Fire - General Correspondence, 1967-68 (Box 15, Folder 51)
      Stamp, Neal R.; Cooch, Thomas. Letter to other universities; Claim settlements; Litigation.
    - New York State College of Agriculture, 1959-63 (Box 15, Folder 52)
      Ward, William B.; Palm, Charles E.; Kennedy, W. Keith. International Agricultural Development.
    - New York State College of Agriculture, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 53)
      Cline, Marlin G.; Larson, Olaf F.; Kennedy, W. Keith. Committee to Plan a Study of the Future Role of the College of Agriculture; International Biological Programme.
    - New York State College of Agriculture, 1964-65 (Box 15, Folder 54)
      Turk, Kenneth L.; Palm, Charles E.; Kennedy, Robert F.; Barton, Donald W.; Lewis, Richard M.; MacEachron, James. National Science Foundation; Center for International Studies; New York State Agricultural Businessmen's Council; Cornell Plantations.
    - New York State College of Agriculture.Palm, Charles E.; Morison, Robert S.; Burke, Arleigh; Leurgans, Paul J. National Academy of Sciences - National Research Council. "International Studies in the Rural Social Science Departments, New York State College of Agriculture. ", 1965 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - New York State College of Agriculture, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      Palm, Charles E.; Boodley, James W.; Everett, Herbert Lyman. Extension education.
    - New York State College of Agriculture, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      Palm, Charles E.; Rockefeller, Nelson A. Concord grape industry; Bioclimatic Laboratories; Advisory Council for the New York State College of Agriculture; Campbell Soup Company; Hydrology Committee.
    - New York State College of Agriculture, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      Palm, Charles E.; Bailey, Liberty Hyde; Kennedy, W. Keith; Watkins, Thomas C. Names change; Films.
    - New York State College of Agriculture, 1965-66 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      Palm, Charles E.; Oyer, Edwin B.; Kennedy, W. Keith; Steward, F. C.; Ward, William B.; Larson, Olaf F.; Lovvorn, Roy; Hedlund, Glenn W.; Young, Robert J. Name changes; Civil Rights Act of 1964; Los Banos Program.
    - New York State College of Agriculture, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      Palm, Charles E.; McDowell, Robert E.; Barton, Donald W.; Turk, Kenneth L.; Robinson, Willard. Name change; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station.
    - New York State College of Agriculture, 1966-68 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      Palm, Charles E.; Rockcastle, Verne N.; Clark, John M.; Adams, Morton; Plaisted, Robert L.; Steward, F. C. Field laboratories; Tenure; Ford Foundation Professorships.
    - New York State College of Agriculture -Department of Agricultural Engineering., 1966 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Livestock Advisory Council, 1961-66 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      Earl, J. Stanley.
    - New York State College of Agriculture -Agronomy Department - Dr. John S. Waid, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      Cline, Marlin G.
    - New York State College of Agriculture - Biometrics Unit, 1960-61 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      Kennedy, W. Keith.
    - Department of Biochemistry, 1963-65 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      Young, Robert J.; O'Brien, Richard D.; Hunter, Kenneth J.; Hess, George P.
    - Department of Botany, 1959-64 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      Palm, Charles E.; Steward, F. C.; Stinson, Harry T.; Kingsbury, John M.; Boynton, Damon.
    - Center for Applied Mathematics, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      Atwood, Sanford S.; Mackesey, Thomas W.; Sears, William R.
    - Center for Applied Mathematics, 1963-65 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      Sears, William R.; Long, Franklin A.
    - College of Arts and sciences - Deanship, 1961-63 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      Scheraga, Harold A. Ad Hoc Committee to Recommend Candidates for the Deanship.
    - Thirteenth Field Emissions Symposium, 6-10 September., 1966 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Laboratory of Atomic and Solid State Physics, 1961-63 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      Krumhansl, James A. Materials Science Center.
    - Laboratory of Atomic and Solid State Physics, 1963-67 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      Rhodin, Thor N.; Krumhansl, James A.
    - Department of Physics, 1956-63 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      Carruthers, Peter A.; Parratt, Lyman G.; Cliggott, Richard T.; Wright, Theodore P. National Carbon Company.
    - Department of Physics, 1963-66 (Box 16, Folder 21)
      Parratt, Lyman G.; Palmberg, Paul William; Skolnick, Malcolm; Hartman, Paul; Cotts, Robert M.; Gold, Thomas; Ney, Ed. Advanced Physics Laboratory Course; International Conference on the Physics of X-Rays; Physics Council; Physics Graduate Conference; Courses.
    - Department of Physics. Bethe, Hans A.; Brown, Stuart M.; Parratt, Lyman G.; Holcomb, Donald F.; Wilson, Robert R.; Salpeter, Edwin E. Physics Graduate Conference; "An Anecdotal Account of Accelerators at Cornell (For Bethe 's Festschrift)" by Wilson., 1966-67 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Physical Sciences Building, 1961-62 (Box 16, Folder 23)
      Krumhansl, James A.; Olin, John M.; Atwood, Sanford S.
    - Physical Sciences Building, 1961-62 (Box 16, Folder 24)
      "The New Physical Sciences Building"; "A Capsule History of Rockefeller Hall"; Advanced Research Projects Agency; National Science Foundation.
    - College of Engineering, 1959-61 (Box 16, Folder 25)
      Sack, Henri S. Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory; Courses; "The Next Ten to Twenty Years in Engineering Education at Cornell University" by Dale R. Corson; Common Freshmen Year.
    - College of Engineering. Furnas, Clifford C.; Fretwell, Elbert K.; Dean, Arthur H.; Atwood, Sanford S.; Sporn, Philip. Department of Defense, Director of Defense Research and Engineering; "Problems of Graduate Education and Research at Cornell"; Engineering degree programs;Fifth year honors graduate program., 1962-63 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - College of Engineering, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 27)
      Bard, Francis N.; Gebhart, Benjamin; Moyer, Donald H.; Howe, John P.; Schultz, Andrew S. Bausch and Lomb, Inc.; Engineering degree programs; Center for Environmental Systems Analysis (Proposed).
    - College of Engineering.Schultz, Andrew S.; Charnes, Abraham; Batterman, Boris W. Center for Environmental Systems Analysis (Proposed); "Cornell and its Future in Engineering. ", 1964 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - College of Engineering, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 29)
      Fisher, Gordon P.; Ruoff, Arthur L.; Moyer, Donald H.; Detweiler, A. Henry; Schultz, Andrew S.; Gaver, Donald P. Rochester Gas and Electric Company; DuPont Company; New York State Technical Services Act of 1965.
    - College of Engineering, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 30)
      Berth, Donald F.; Fischer, Patrick T.; Schultz, Andrew S. Engineering College Council; Laboratory equipment.
    - College of Engineering, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 31)
      Cowie, Robert A.; Howe, John P.; Borgmann, Carl W.; Requardt, Gustav J.; Schultz, Andrew S.; Owen, Walter S.; Carlin, Herbert J. Ad Hoc Committee to Review Engineering Physics Activity in the College of Engineering; Cornell Society of Engineers; Ford Foundation Program in Science and Engineering; "A Succinct Statement of Engineering College Needs" by Andrew Schultz.
    - College of Engineering, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 32)
      Schultz, Andrew S.; Requardt, Gustav J. Ford Foundation; Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities of the State of New York; Engineers' Council for Professional Development; Harrison D. McFaddin Fund; Space needs.
    - College of Engineering, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 33)
      AVCO Corporation; "Experimental Curriculum for the First Four Semesters of Engineering"; Continuing Education and Curricular Conference.
    - College of Engineering, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 34)
      Farley, Donald; Cisler, Walker L.; Ward, J. Carlton. Plasma Research.
    - Ford Foundation Professors in the College of Engineering, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 35)
      McDaniel, Joseph M.; Schultz, Andrew S.
    - Oberman, Carl Raymond., 1966 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Computing Center. Lesser, Richard C.; Hastie, John W.; Wright, Theodore P.; Rosenblatt, Frank; Malott, Deane W.; Watson, Thomas J. National Science Foundation; Burroughs Corporation; Computers; IBM; Perceptron Project., 1958-59 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Computing Center. Lesser, Richard C.; Peterson, Arthur H.; Walker, Robert J. Coordinating Committee on Computing., 1960-63 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Computing Center. Lesser, Richard C.; Long, Franklin A. Alfred P. Sloan Foundation., 1964-65 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Computing Center.Conway, Richard W.; Long, Franklin A. United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare; Langmuir Laboratory; "A Proposal for the Organization of Data Processing Facilities at Cornell. ", 1964-66 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Computing Center, 1966-67 (Box 16, Folder 41)
      Long, Franklin A.; Conway, Richard W. IBM; Alfred P. Sloan Foundation; National Institutes of Health; National Science Foundation.
    - Computing Center. Long, Franklin A.; Conway, Richard W. IBM., 1967 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - College of Engineering Deanship Committee. Schultz, Andrew S., 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Nuclear Reactor. Wright, Theodore P.; Cisler, Walker L. Atomic Energy Commission; "Proposal for a Nuclear Technology Center. ", 1957-58 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Nuclear Reactor, 1957-64 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Wright, Theodore P.; Ward, J. Carlton; Cuykendall, Trevor R. Vitro Corporation; Cornell University Laboratory of Nuclear Studies; Nuclear Reactor Committee.
    - Final Report, Office of Naval Research, n. d. (Box 17, Folder 3)
      Wilson, Robert R.; McDaniel, Boyce D.
    - Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Financial Assistance in Establishment of a Center for Nuclear Technology., 1959 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Cornell Dual-Core Reactor., 1958 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Graduate School. Boynton, Damon; Cooke, W. Donald; Srb, Adrian M.; Cartter, Allan M. Admissions quotas; Supply of faculty., 1964-65 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Graduate School, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      Cooke, W. Donald; Sackinger, William M. Graduate faculty; Humanities fellowships; Admissions quotas.
    - Graduate School, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Cooke, W. Donald; Cole, LaMont C.; Parrish, Stephen M. Teaching assistantships; Graduate Study Committee on the Foreign Language Requirement; Ecology and Systematics; Support for the Humanities; Humanities fellowships.
    - Graduate School, 1965-66 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      Cooke, W. Donald; Sproull, Robert L. Fellowships.
    - Graduate School, 1966-68 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      Carter, Lisle C.; diPace, Maria J.; Long, Franklin A. Ford Foundation; Graduate Fellowship Program.
    - Graduate School - Code of Legislation of the Graduate Faculty., 1963 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Graduate School - Study Committee Reports., 1965 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Graduate School - Graduate Fellowship Program., 1965 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Graduate School Record, Ohio State University., 1965 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Graduate School - Confidential Report by the Dean to the President., 1965 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Graduate School - Report on the Quality of Graduate Students., 1965 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Graduate School - Ford Foundation Proposal."A Proposal to the Ford Foundation for a Four Year Ph. D. Program. ", 1966 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Graduate School - Ford Foundation Grant, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      Cooke, W. Donald.
    - "Graduate Training and the 'Facts of Life'" by Gelia Tagumpay Castillo., 1966 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - New York State College of Home Economics. Canoyer, Helen G.; Carreiro, Joseph., 1963-65 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - New York State College of Home Economics, 1965-66 (Box 17, Folder 21)
      Canoyer, Helen G.; Steininger, Grace; Brittain, W. Lambert; Bayer, Helen; Bronfenbrenner, Urie; Feldman, Harold. Cornell-Ghana Home Economics Project.
    - New York State College of Home Economics. Canoyer, Helen G.; Vatter, Ethel; Devereux, Edward C. Cornell-Ghana Home Economics Project; Department of Child Development and Family Relationships; College Study Committee; Name change; International Newsletter; Oakes Japanese Art Collection; Budget request justification., 1966 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - New York State College of Home Economics Faculty Committee on Admissions, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      Humphreyville, Theresa.
    - New York state College of Home Economics Cornell-Ghana Home Economics Project, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 24)
      Wood, Mary B. Memorandum of Understanding.
    - School of Hotel Administration, 1962-65 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      Beck, Robert A.; Arbury, Ward B.; Mackesey, Thomas W.; Statler, Alice G.; McHugh, William F. Statler Foundation; Cornell University Board of Trustees; Statler Hall addition; E. M. Statler Chair of Hotel Administration.
    - School of Hotel Administration, 1965-66 (Box 17, Folder 26)
      Beck, Robert A.; Arbury, Ward B.; MacLennan, H. Alexander. Statler Foundation; Morris Brown College; Selective Service; Ready foods; Statler Hall addition; New York State Dormitory Authority.
    - School of Hotel Administration Data Processing, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      Beck, Robert A. Statler Foundation; Establishment of a Data Processing Center for a Group of New York City Hotels.
    - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, 1965-66 (Box 17, Folder 28)
      Moore, David G.; Whyte, William Foote; Wilhelm, Harry E. Ford Foundation; Wilhelm Weinberg Labor-Management Seminar; Publication contracts.
    - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations Academic Plan., 1965-66 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations Faculty Meeting Minutes., 1964-66 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations Special Extension Report., n. d. (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations - Miscellaneous Summaries., n. d. (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Cornell Law School, 1964-66 (Box 17, Folder 33)
      Forrester, Ray; Mignano, Mary; Hacker, Andrew; Franck, Thomas M.; Fisher, Gordon P. Latin American Research Review.
    - Cornell Law School - Reports and Publications., 1964-66 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center, 1965-67 (Box 17, Folder 35)
      Luckey, E. Hugh. Rockefeller Foundation; Samuel J. and Evelyn L. Wood Foundation.
    - Cornell University Medical college, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 36)
      Deitrick, John E.; Moore, John K. IBM; Associated Medical Schools of Greater New York.
    - Cornell University Medical College, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 37)
      Stamp, Neal R.; Bailey, Norman T. J.; Luckey, E. Hugh; Deitrick, John E. Rockefeller Foundation; Knight and Gladieux, Management Consultants.
    - Cornell University Medical College, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 38)
      Luckey, E. Hugh; Deitrick, John E.; Hinsey, Joseph C.; Stamp, Neal R. SUNY; New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center Joint Administrative Board.
    - Cornell University Medical College Agreements., 1967 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Cornell University Medical College Committee on Medical Scientist Training., 1967 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Cornell University Medical College - Regional Medical Program Planning Grant., 1966 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center Joint Administrative Board., 1966-67 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center Joint Administrative Board., 1967 (Box 17, Folder 43, Folder 45)
    - New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center Joint Administrative Board., 1968 (Box 17, Folder 46, Folder 47)
    - Accounts - Salaries., 1968-69 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Accounts - General Expenses., 1968-69 (Box 18, Folder 2, Folder 4)
    - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory, 1965-66 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      Green, Alvin E.; Beal, John L.; Orear, Jay; Long, Franklin A.; Ross, Ira G. Federation of American Scientists; Brookhaven National Laboratory; Cornell Newsletter; Classified research; "Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory - Its Character, Mission and Accomplishments"; Automotive Crash Injury Program.
    - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory, 1965-66 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      Stamp, Neal R.; Ross, Ira G.; Wright, Theodore P.; Schultz, Andrew S.; da Cunha, Haroldo Lisboa. Expansion of facilities; Board of Directors; Professorships.
    - Campus Store - Provost's Report, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      Provost's Ad Hoc Committee on the Campus Store.
    - Cornell University-Hampton Institute Exchange Program., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - London-Cornell Project, 1968-69 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      Golay, Frank H.; Lopez, Salvador P.; Einaudi, Mario; Lewis, John W. Carnegie Corporation.
    - Emergency Procedures., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Intersession, 1967-68 (Box 18, Folder 11, Folder 13)
      Moyer, Donald H.
    - Microfilm. Williams, Herbert H. Eastman Kodak Company., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Class of 1909 Men - G. J. Requardt. Requardt, Gustav J.; Todd, Walter L.; Farr, Newton C.; Myers, William I., 1965-66 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Class of 1909 Men - 6. J. Requardt, 1966-68 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      Requardt, Gustav J.; Todd, Walter L.; Farr, Newton C.
    - Science Writers Conference, 1967-68 (Box 18, Folder 17)